{
    "id": "e10dd81e93e64229a3b7c382d18b4081",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "A grandparent's job is easier than  ..............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a parent",
                "a parent's",
                "that of a parent"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Are the banks ........................... on Saturdays?",
            "description": "We use open as an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "open",
                "opened",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Who left the faucets ....................................?",
            "description": "We do not open faucets. We turn them on.",
            "answers": [
                "open",
                "turned on",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you ..................................... this shoelace?",
            "description": "We do not open shoelaces.",
            "answers": [
                "undo",
                "untie",
                "open"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ought to be here soon, ....................................?",
            "description": "Contracted negative forms of ought are rare in American English.",
            "answers": [
                "oughtn't he",
                "ought he",
                "shouldn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You ought ............................. go.",
            "description": "In negative clauses not comes before to.",
            "answers": [
                "not to",
                "to not",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran ................................ the room.",
            "description": "The opposite of into is out of.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "out of",
                "out from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will do it in ................................ way.",
            "description": "Myself does not have a possessive form.",
            "answers": [
                "myself's",
                "myself",
                "my own"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She lives ..................................",
            "description": "When people live on their own, they live without company.",
            "answers": [
                "herself",
                "on her",
                "on her own"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I did it ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "myself",
                "on my own",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I was very ................................... in the discussion.",
            "description": "The past participle is used to say how people feel.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "interesting",
                "interested"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn't enjoy the party because I was ...................................",
            "description": "The past participle is used to say how people feel.",
            "answers": [
                "tiring",
                "tired"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}